(foot tapping)
(pencil tapping)
(clock ticking)
(bell rings)
(upbeat music)
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby, how
was I supposed to know ♪
♪ That something wasn't right here ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby, I
shouldn't have let you go ♪
♪ And now you're out of sight, yeah ♪
♪ Show me how you want it to be ♪
♪ Tell me, baby, 'cause I
need to know now, oh because ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ I must confess I still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ The reason I breathe is you ♪
♪ Boy, you got me blinded ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ There's nothing that I wouldn't do ♪
♪ It's not the way I planned it ♪
♪ Show me how you want it to be ♪
♪ Tell me, baby, 'cause I
need to know now, oh because ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ I must confess I still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby, how
was I supposed to know ♪
♪ Oh pretty baby, I
shouldn't have let you go ♪
♪ I must confess, that my
loneliness is killing me now ♪
♪ Don't you know I still believe ♪
♪ That you will be here ♪
♪ And give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ I must confess I still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ I must confess that my loneliness ♪
♪ Is killing me now ♪
♪ Don't you know I still believe ♪
♪ That you will be here ♪
♪ And give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
(bell rings)
(students running)